http://www.matton.com/privacy

Search
> open filtersUpload an image to find similar by drag-and-drop into this box or choose below.Choose a local file to upload:
VIEW BASKET : 0
+
manage my lightboxes
Temp Lightbox
(0)
Company Press : Images
What are Royalty Free Images?
Our Philosophy
Matton is committed to protecting your privacy and any details we use in our work with you. This statement demonstrates how we define, gather and utilize personally identifiable information. Matton continuously takes every reasonable step to protect user privacy as defined within the guidelines set forth in this policy and the law and this statement governs the information practices for this website, http://www.matton.com/.
Personal Information
During the registration process, we ask you for your company or personal address, telephone number, email address and other relevant and useful information. This information is used only for our own purposes, in processing your requests and providing service for your orders of products. Neither your email address, nor any other personal information will be shared with other companies in any event.
Matton may, however, use email to send you information from us and possibly our suppliers, including special offers, newsletters, and press releases. You can request to "opt-out" of these email newsletters at any time by following the instructions in the email message. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary, such as for purchasing issues or support.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect any possible loss, misuse and alteration of the information provided by you to us as we transact business. The Matton website is protected by firewalls and requires user authentication so that only registered customers may access the site. Credit card transactions are processed through a credit card system that uses SSL techniques (Secure Socket Layers), and transmits any necessary financial information through an encrypted link. matton.com does not retain any credit card information for any reason.
Order Processing/Transaction Information
When you place an order on our site, we request you to complete an order form that asks certain information from you including financial information such as a credit card number and expiration date. This information helps us to complete the transaction that you have requested and to deliver information, products or other services that you order and to invoice you. We do not store your credit card information, but we do store your mailing and shipping addresses and other contact information. Relevant information from your order is used to send orders and information about our company to you as requested. Matton is a distributor of licensable content and some of the customer's contact and order information is also required by federal law to be provided to the owner or "copyright owner" of any licensed content. However, no financial information of any kind is provided to the copyright owner of any licensed content except for the total license price. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary for supporting you and your use of the licensed products. Often, we will run contests on our site where we may ask visitors for various contact information. We use this data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor if and when necessary.
Cookies
As with most web sites, matton.com assigns you with a unique number for tracking your types of images and preferences in searching our content libraries. This number is stored in a file on your computer and is called a "cookie." This provides you with the functions to automatically login to our site and it allows us to track how visitors use our site. We assess this data for trends and use all this information in order to improve our services to you, plan future products and measure overall site effectiveness.
Sharing Information
Matton does not ever disclose any of your personal data to other companies. However, we do generally disclose data of a general and medium nature such as user statistics, in order to describe our services to prospective partners and other third parties.
Password
Your Matton User Account Information is password-protected in order to secure your personal information. We strongly suggest that you do not pass on your password to anyone in any correspondence or transmissions. If you share a computer with someone else or others have access to the same computer, remember to close your browser window when you have finished so that others cannot access your personal data, especially if you are using a computer in a public place such as a library or "shared environment".
Legal Requirements
Matton may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law.
Matton may modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time.
Key points from Matton's Privacy Policy
We use cookies
These small files help give you a more personalized experience.
Cookies are commonly used by most sites on the Internet.
We do NOT share your information
Any information you give us remains private and secure.
We only email when you opt-in to receive it
We occasionally send interesting offers by email.
We only email registered users, and you can opt out from receiving these emails at anytime.
BUY NOW DOWNLOAD NOW
+
feedback
Your one-stop royalty free stock shop :
-
